<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <array name="images">
    <item>@drawable/labrador</item>
    <item>@drawable/malamute</item>
    <item>@drawable/husky</item>
    <item>@drawable/pomeranian</item>
    <item>@drawable/redbone</item>
    <item>@drawable/rottweiler</item>
    <item>@drawable/sheepdog</item>
    <item>@drawable/springer</item>
  </array>

  <string-array name="names">
    <item>Labrador</item>
    <item>Malamute</item>
    <item>Siberian Husky</item>
    <item>Pomeranian</item>
    <item>Redbone</item>
    <item>Rottweiler</item>
    <item>Belgian Sheepdog</item>
    <item>Welsh Springer</item>
  </string-array>

  <string-array name="descriptions">
    <item>The sweet-faced, lovable Labrador Retriever is America’s most popular dog breed. Labs are
      friendly, outgoing, and high-spirited companions.</item>
    <item>An immensely strong, heavy-duty worker of spitz type, the Alaskan Malamute is an
      affectionate, loyal, and playful but dignified dog recognizable by his well-furred plumed
      tail carried over the back, erect ears, and substantial bone.</item>
    <item>The Siberian Husky, a thickly coated, compact sled dog of medium size and great
      endurance, was developed to work in packs, pulling light loads at moderate speeds over vast
      frozen expanses. Huskies are friendly, fastidious, and dignified.</item>
    <item>The tiny Pomeranian, long a favorite of royals and commoners alike, has been called the
      ideal companion. The glorious coat, smiling, foxy face, and vivacious personality have helped
      make the Pom one of the world\'s most popular toy breeds.</item>
    <item>The streamlined Redbone Coonhound, an American original, is even-tempered, mellow, and
      kindly at home but a tiger on the trail. Vigorous activities like hunting and swimming
      between long periods of rest is the rhythm of coonhound life.</item>
    <item>The Rottweiler is a robust working, gentle playmate and protector within the family
      circle, the Rottie observes the outside world with a self-assured aloofness.</item>
    <item>The Belgian Sheepdog is a highly trainable herder whose versatility and intelligence is
      the stuff of canine legend. This is a breed built for hard work, and plenty of it. These
      sensitive souls crave human companionship and abhor neglect.</item>
    <item>The Welsh Springer Spaniel is a vigorous, medium-sized bird dog of happy disposition,
      known for versatility in the field, companionability at home, and dashing good looks
      anywhere. The Welshie is among Britain\'s oldest sporting breeds.</item>
  </string-array>

  <string-array name="urls">
    <item>https://www.akc.org/dog-breeds/labrador-retriever/</item>
    <item>https://www.akc.org/dog-breeds/alaskan-malamute/</item>
    <item>https://www.akc.org/dog-breeds/siberian-husky/</item>
    <item>https://www.akc.org/dog-breeds/pomeranian/</item>
    <item>https://www.akc.org/dog-breeds/redbone-coonhound/</item>
    <item>https://www.akc.org/dog-breeds/rottweiler/</item>
    <item>https://www.akc.org/dog-breeds/belgian-sheepdog/</item>
    <item>https://www.akc.org/dog-breeds/welsh-springer-spaniel/</item>
  </string-array>
</resources>